Freshman Father is a drama, tv movie film directed by Michael M. Scott.
When high school sweethearts John and Kathy find out Kathy is pregnant, they decide to get
married and move to Cambridge so John can fulfill his scholarship to Harvard.
But faced with the harsh reality of their situation, Kathy leaves John behind, compelling him to rent a room
from Dorothy, a psychic who encourages him as he struggles to balance school and fatherhood.
John Patton, played by Drew Seeley.
Kathy Patton, played by Britt Irvin.
Dorothy Downs, played by Annie Potts.
Mrs. Patton, played by Merrilyn Gann.
Marion Blair, played by Barbara Tyson.
Danny, played by Anthony Shim.
Freshman Father is an American-Canadian television drama
film directed by Michael Scott, aired in 2010.
It is inspired by a true story of John Wand in 1970.
The tone is emotional.